my first feelings
hajimete no kimochi
はじめての気持ち
upon my downhearted chest
shonbori no mune ni
しょんぼりの胸に
a sunny ray of light was gently thrown
potto nagerareta hidamarine
ぽっと投げられた陽だまりね
walking alone...
hitori aruiteta
ひとり歩いてた
when I looked up at the sky,
sora miageta toki
空みあげた時
spring was near,
haru ga soko ni kiteta
春がそこに来てた
it showed me
misetekureta
見せてくれた
these trembling feelings are
kogareru omoiwa
焦がれる想いは
fluttering petals,
maichiru hanabirane
舞い散る花びらね
is it okay for me to fall in love?
sukininatte iino
好きになっていいの？
or will...
soretomo
それとも
my hesitating heart
tamerau kokoro ga
ためらう心が
put on my brakes,
bureiki kakerukedo
ブレーキかけるけど
it's so painful
kurushikute
苦しくて
I can't breathe
ikiga tomarisou desu
息が止まりそうです
First Flower
It’s been a while since I’ve stopped caring about the changing of the seasons.
Please keep the
restrooms clean
Shirafuji.
Please keep the
restrooms clean
Shirafuji.
Please keep the
restrooms clean
Passengers headed to Manase,
please wait for the express train that arrives next.
How much meaning is there to the fact that it is spring right now?
I've fallen in love with someone else.
Oh... I see.
Tsubana. Tsubana.
Please wait until the train has come to a complete stop.
Excuse me, I’m getting off.
H-Hey... Excuse me.
Hey, you there!
Hey, student!
Yes?
Oh... Here.
Oh, no. I didn't realize I'd dropped it.
Thank you very much.
You’re welcome.
Machida Marriage Consulting
That’s all I have about the next arranged marriage party.
If nobody has any questions, then I would like to end the meeting.
Yes!
Odagiri.
This party is restricted to members in their late twenties to early thirties.
However, I suggest we lower the age requirement,
and create a party comprised solely of teenage girls—
That’s all!
Good work, guys.
Let’s go eat!
Where do you want to go?
Didn’t a new restaurant open up in Kanami?
Really?
Koshiro.
Huh?
You’re sorting the membership data files in the back today.
Why?
That face... And that smell!
I can’t show that to our customers.
Reference Room
The toilet is
in the front.
I'm certain there's a demand.
You think so?
From experience, men my age can only meet teenage girls illegally.
So, it’s just your demand.
I wonder if I'll get a chance to meet a female high school student?
You just keep working.
I’m ho...me.
I wasn’t told about this!
Anyway, you’re going to be living with Nanoka starting tomorrow night.
Prepare yourself!
So suddenly...
I wanted you to meet Nanoka.
You remember her, don't you?
Yes, I do.
I do remember her, though I don’t remember her face.
She’s a freshman now.
Fifteen years old. She's so cute!
Lots of students commute long-distance nowadays.
Her commute time will be reduced from two hours to one!
Isn’t it reasonable to let her stay here?
You're not trying to get back together with Mom
just because your lover dumped you, are you?
That’s not how it is!
It’s not?
No!
She’s my daughter!
She’s family!
Your younger sister!
Living my carefree life with Dad,
I sometimes forget:
I have a mother and a sister who’s twelve years my junior.
Please introduce her to me!
What the hell are you thinking?
Why were you hiding something so important from me?!
I wasn’t really hiding it.
We simply don't even know each other.
My parents are divorced.
Even though I've met my mom, who took custody of her, a few times,
I haven’t seen my sister at all.
You have a customer!
Machida Marriage Consulting
Sorry to keep you waiting.
So...
What kind of man are you interested in?
Don’t be mad.
I’m sorry for bothering you at work.
It’s all right.
I'm on lunch break anyway.
I came to get the keys to my place back.
I felt it would be more appropriate to do this during the day.
Just a minute.
Well, then.
Yeah.
You’re really letting me go without a fuss.
Sorry.
But...
You just accepted it so easily.
I just thought,
“Oh, I didn't mean that much to to you”.
Koshiro, have you ever loved anyone from the bottom of your heart?
What should I have done, then?
There are three events planned to happen during the party,
so we'd like the food to be served at the right times.
Next, concerning the audio equipment...
Thank you for your business.
Thank you.
Oh, right.
Sakuragaoka Amusement Park
Here. These are for the place next door.
Oh, thank you very much.  Don’t mind if I do.
What do I say to a woman who says she's in love with someone else?
What should I have done?
What a great view.
This place kind of hurts for a bachelor.
Sakuragaoka
Amusement Park
So you broke up?
Sakuragaoka
Amusement Park
Yeah.
Sakuragaoka
You’re so cool about it.
Amusement Park
Sakuragaoka
That’s what she disliked about me.
Amusement Park
Here, I’ll give these to you.
I don’t need them.
Why don’t you try asking the girl you just broke up with?
Maybe you two will get back together.
Who the hell’d want to get back together with—
Ah! Hello.
Do you remember me?
Yesterday morning.
Yeah, I remember!
I remember you.
Ah, I’m glad.
Such a naughty boy!
Asking out high school girls?
That’s not how it is!
Thank you for yesterday.
I’m sorry for interrupting your date.
That’s wrong too!
Hey!
Well...
Yes?
Here.
Please take these.
Idiot.
Umm...
This is perfect. I was waiting to meet someone,
but I arrived too early and needed to kill time.
Meet someone?
Yes. My father.
Hey, what would you like to ride?
Are you all right?
What the hell am I doing?
Here.
Wow! Thank you very much.
I’m sorry.
It must be boring to be with me.
Not at all.
Don’t you have a boyfriend?
I just got rejected by someone.
Wow! It’s so beautiful!
This...
I received this during my junior high graduation...
From the person I liked.
But it wasn’t his second button.
In Japan, it is a tradition upon graduation to give the second button from your school uniform to the girl you like.
I liked him ever since I was a first-year.
He wasn't really handsome or anything,
but I really liked him.
I gathered up all my courage and confessed to him, but...
He said he’s going out with a junior.
I didn’t know about it at all.
If the window could be opened,
I would throw it out from here.
What a shame.
Don’t say you’ll throw it away.
You still like him, don’t you?
So don’t say that you’ll throw it away.
But...
I have to forget about him.
He has someone that he’s going out with.
We go to different schools now.
I can't even see him anymore.
So why?
Why would you say that?
You’re so straightforward.
How is it...
How can you love someone so frankly and honestly?
I...
I just got dumped too.
Well, it’s rather different than your situation.
My feelings totally cooled off.
I don’t really know if I ever even loved her.
But...
That’s why...
You should definitely treasure...
those heartfelt emotions.
Huh?
Why am I...?
I was so surprised.
The cherry blossoms.
Since I got rejected, I've been walking with my head down,
so I didn’t notice the cherry blossoms at all.
When you stopped me at the train station,
I noticed them for the first time.
I was really surprised!
The petals were falling like snow,
and for a moment I felt like I was in a different world.
It was the same for me.
Where is this...
this place that I’ve always been?
Is it possible for me to stay here forever?
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Umm...
No, it’s nothing.
Well, I have to...
Hey!
Sorry I’m late.
Dad!
Father?
Huh?!
Oh, you’re here too, Koshiro?
It’s been so long since you siblings have gotten together.
Did you two recognize each other right away?
Hey, what’s wrong with the two of you? Let’s go!
Hey...!
What should we have for dinner?
Nanoka, what do you want?
Wait...
Dad...
Brother?
That's right.
I have...
A little sister.
A gentle dream
yasashii yume ga
やさしい夢が
calls the spring in my heart
sotto mune no haru wo yobi
そっと胸の春を呼び
and becomes a gentle breeze
yasashii kaze ni nari
やさしい風になり
that touches you then leaves
kimi ni furete satteyuku
君に触れて去ってゆく
in the small pot
chiisana potto ni wa
小さなポットには
are feelings of love
daisukina kimochi
大好きな気持ち
swaying softly
yurayura to
ゆらゆらと
that carry a sweet scent
ii kaori nosete
いい香りのせて
always waiting...
itsumo matteita
いつも待っていた
warming up this moment...
kono toki wo atatamete
この時をあたためて
We understand each other
futari dakara wakaru koto
ふたりだからわかる
without words
kotoba janakute
言葉じゃなくて
we just smile, we just hope
hohoemu dake negaudake
ほほえむだけ　願うだけ
to the quiet sky
shizukana sora e
しずかな空へ
we'll see each other again tomorrow...
ashita mo mata aeru yo ne
あしたもまた会えるよね
at the quiet sky
shizukana sora de
しずかな空で