my first feelings
hajimete no kimochi
はじめての気持ち
upon my downhearted chest
shonbori no mune ni
しょんぼりの胸に
a sunny ray of light was gently thrown
potto nagerareta hidamarine
ぽっと投げられた陽だまりね
walking alone...
hitori aruiteta
ひとり歩いてた
when I looked up at the sky,
sora miageta toki
空みあげた時
spring was near,
haru ga soko ni kiteta
春がそこに来てた
it showed me
misetekureta
見せてくれた
these trembling feelings are
kogareru omoiwa
焦がれる想いは
fluttering petals,
maichiru hanabirane
舞い散る花びらね
is it okay for me to fall in love?
sukininatte iino
好きになっていいの？
or will...
soretomo
それとも
my hesitating heart
tamerau kokoro ga
ためらう心が
put on my brakes,
bureiki kakerukedo
ブレーキかけるけど
it's so painful
kurushikute
苦しくて
I can't breathe
ikiga tomarisou desu
息が止まりそうです
Distant Thunder
Hey, Daddy, will there be a panda? A panda?
What? A panda?
Well, I'm leaving now.
Unbelievable.
You're still here?
Onii-chan, if you have nothing to do, could you at least clean the bathtub?
Did she notice?
It was only for an instant.
There's no way.
There's no way...
Onii-chan.
What should we have for lunch? Is soumen okay?
soumen = cold white noodles, eaten during summer
Dad hasn't come back since he left to get his hair cut.
Let's just go ahead and eat-
You went into my room, didn't you?
Yeah.
Tomorrow is garbage day, so I...
I've told you before, haven't I? Not to go in without my permission.
But... all I did was empty your waste basket. I didn't touch anything else...
That's not the problem!
I'm saying that I'll take care of my own trash!
You wouldn't like it if I went into your room right?
I'm sorry.
You're right.
Idiot. You're just too inconsiderate.
You don't have to put it like that...
I was just trying to be nice.
Nobody asked you to!
Don't make me repeat myself again.
What was that?
Insinuation?
No. No way...
It was just for an instant.
There's no way she could have noticed.
But...
That's suspicious.
Really?
Definitely suspicious. Why would he get so angry for just going into his room?
Maybe there was something he really didn't want you to see.
Ah, I know!
What? What?
A present.
He makes himself seem like a major jerk,
and tomorrow he'll suddenly transform into the nice big brother.
Ah! That kind of a plan!
Nanoka, it's your birthday tomorrow right?
No way! No way! That's definitely not it!
Maybe Nanoka's big brother is pretty simple minded.
Marriage
Consulting
That's not a bamboo tree anymore...
It is the Tanabata matchmaking Party.
Tanabata = festival of the Weaver, celebrated on July 7th
The mood is very important to young women!
Young women?
Proposal for the "Star Festival Matchmaking Party"
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the "Star Festival Matchmaking Party"
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the "Star Festival Matchmaking Party"
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the "Star Festival Matchmaking Party"
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the "Star Festival Matchmaking Party"
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the "Star Festival Matchmaking Party"
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the "Star Festival Matchmaking Party"
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the "Star Festival Matchmaking Party"
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the "Star Festival Matchmaking Party"
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the "Star Festival Matchmaking Party"
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the "Star Festival Matchmaking Party"
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the "Star Festival Matchmaking Party"
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the "Star Festival Matchmaking Party"
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the "Star Festival Matchmaking Party"
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the "Star Festival Matchmaking Party"
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the "Star Festival Matchmaking Party"
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the "Star Festival Matchmaking Party"
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the "Star Festival Matchmaking Party"
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Proposal for the "Star Festival Matchmaking Party"
Targets: Female Members
Age Fifteen to Marriage Age
Wha... What are you...!
The guy over there, decorating the bamboos with tanzaku without complaining...
it looks really ominous.
I want to
have a
younger
sister.
Odagiri
Wha... What are you doing?
I'm telling you, there's nothing good about having a younger sister.
A guy who fights over the TV channels with his cute younger sister wouldn't understand my feelings!
Man its steaming out here.
Going outside is the worst.
Do you want to go for a drink?
Sure! I was just about to ask you.
Is it all right not to call home?
After Nanoka-chan came, you've been calling home every time you're going to be late, right?
No I haven't.
There's no use hiding it.
Why don't you wipe your mouth?!
I don't care about her.
She's the one who just suddenly came into my life.
I don't give a damn about her.
I really don't give a damn about a girl like her...
Onii-chan?
Don't come near me!
It's dangerous with the broken pieces.
That's my bowl.
It was my favorite bowl! What are you going to do?
I won't be able to eat my rice tomorrow.
Umm... Onii-chan...
Do you know what day it is tomorrow?
I have to go out early tomorrow too, so I won't need a lunch.
Just say it.
That I'm sorry I sniffed it.
I'm sorry for feeling a sexual desire.
No.
What good would saying that do?
She might still have the same piece of underwear on from that time, without knowing anything.
From that time...
What? Koshiro left really early today too.
Does he know that it's your birthday today?
It's fine...
that he isn't here.
"I don't need
a big brother."
The father's
free translation.
"I don't need
a big brother."
The father's
free translation.
"I don't need
a big brother."
The father's
free translation.
"I don't need
a big brother."
The father's
free translation.
"I don't need
a big brother."
The father's
free translation.
"I don't need
a big brother."
The father's
free translation.
"I don't need
a big brother."
The father's
free translation.
"I'm happy as long
as you're here, Dad."
Zenzo
"I'm happy as long
as you're here, Dad."
Zenzo
"I'm happy as long
as you're here, Dad."
Zenzo
"I'm happy as long
as you're here, Dad."
Zenzo
"I'm happy as long
as you're here, Dad."
Zenzo
"I'm happy as long
as you're here, Dad."
Zenzo
"I'm happy as long
as you're here, Dad."
Zenzo
"I'm happy as long
as you're here, Dad."
Zenzo
"I'm happy as long
as you're here, Dad."
Zenzo
"I'm happy as long
as you're here, Dad."
Zenzo
Our shelter is a small and creative one... This place is...
Ah I know!
What? What?
A present.
He makes himself seem like a major jerk
and tomorrow hell suddenly transform into the nice big brother.
Ah! That kind of a plan!
Nanoka its your birthday tomorrow right?
I want to
have a
younger
sister.
Odagiri
Your father called.
Nanoka chan left without taking an umbrella, so he asked you to wait for her at the station.
Why me?
He can't leave because he's preparing her birthday party.
Birthday party?
This is why you...
Umm...
Onii-chan...
Do you know what day it is tomorrow?
Why don't you go for her? I don't mind if you leave early—
I just don't get it.
This is my chance...
to use her birthday to fix everything.
I can say "Congratulations!" or "I'm sorry I forgot about it!" and
bring up all these plans and make her happy!
She's so simple-minded, so if I give her some flowers or something she'll probably cry and thank me.
This way I can get rid of my guilt!
Ticket Gate to Manase
I can probably...
I can...
I'm sorry...
No... No! Damn!
There's nothing I can do! I'm the worst!
God I'm the worst!
No, no, no, that's not it!
I'm sorry I forgot about your birthday... And I wanted to say sorry!
There's no deeper meaning in this...
It's okay.
Did you come to get me?
No this isn't for that...
Is that for me?
No way! It's for the Buddha!
I'm glad.
I thought you were really mad at me because I saw you naked in the bathroom.
Why would I get mad?
It's normal to be just in my underwear the whole day with this weather.
Eh? It is?
Yeah.
I see...
I'm sorry.
Yeah! You were really scary last night!
For your birthday present,
I'll buy you whatever you want.
Really?
Then...
Shop
Yamazato
I was supposed to be able to do it...
To get rid... of my guilt...
Why?
a gentle dream
yasashii yume ga
やさしい夢が
calls the spring in my heart
sotto mune no haru wo yobi
そっと胸の春を呼び
and becomes a gentle breeze
yasashii kaze ni nari
やさしい風になり
that touches you then leaves
kimi ni furete satteyuku
君に触れて去ってゆく
in the small pot
chiisana potto ni wa
小さなポットには
are feelings of love
daisukina kimochi
大好きな気持ち
swaying softly
yurayura to
ゆらゆらと
that carry a sweet scent
ii kaori nosete
いい香りのせて
always waiting...
itsumo matteita
いつも待っていた
warming up this moment...
kono toki wo atatamete
この時をあたためて
things we understand because it's the two of us
futari dakara wakaru koto
ふたりだからわかる
are not just words
kotoba janakute
言葉じゃなくて
we just smile, we just hope
hohoemu dake negaudake
ほほえむだけ　願うだけ
to the quiet sky
shizukana sora e
しずかな空へ
we'll see each other again tomorrow...
ashita mo mata aeru yo ne
あしたもまた会えるよね
at the quiet sky
shizukana sora de
しずかな空で