my first feelings
hajimete no kimochi
はじめての気持ち
upon my downhearted chest
shonbori no mune ni
しょんぼりの胸に
a sunny ray of light was gently thrown
potto nagerareta hidamarine
ぽっと投げられた陽だまりね
walking alone...
hitori aruiteta
ひとり歩いてた
when I looked up at the sky,
sora miageta toki
空みあげた時
spring was near,
haru ga soko ni kiteta
春がそこに来てた
it showed me
misetekureta
見せてくれた
these trembling feelings are
kogareru omoiwa
焦がれる想いは
fluttering petals,
maichiru hanabirane
舞い散る花びらね
is it okay for me to fall in love?
sukininatte iino
好きになっていいの？
or will...
soretomo
それとも
my hesitating heart
tamerau kokoro ga
ためらう心が
put on my brakes,
bureiki kakerukedo
ブレーキかけるけど
it's so painful
kurushikute
苦しくて
I can't breathe
ikiga tomarisou desu
息が止まりそうです
I want to touch her.
I want to hold her tight.
I want to be closer to her.
No...
I am such a pervert.
No!
Wintry moon
It's not like I wanted to hurt her.
Good morning!
Good morning.
Is she... still sleeping?
Nanoka already left.
She said she had to leave early.
I see...
Come on, let's eat.
She won't even give me a chance to apologize, huh?
No, maybe there isn't even a need for that anymore.
If I just disappear from her life, won't that solve everything?
Don't say it!
Siblings can't just say they love each other.
Saying that you love your sibling like that...
Something's wrong with you.
I know that it's strange.
I got a bit ahead of myself.
"What do you think of me?"
I shouldn't have asked such a shameless question.
But then, why did he...?
You're moving? Why?
A man your age living in your parent's home...
I was so envious of your situation.
Stuff happened.
You... do understand how busy the office is during this season.
We have a Christmas party, and end of the year party, a New Year's party,
and in just a few more weeks there's going to be a Valentine's party.
In other words, it's going to be a hellish time of party planning.
And you say you're moving tomorrow?!
A lot happened.
So I guess you've already found your apartment?
Not yet.
Anywhere in mind?
None.
Well, what are you going to do?
Who knows?
Then decide now while we're working outside!
Hey, stop.
What do you think?
If there are any conditions you want, let's hear it.
But I believe there's enough to suit you in here already.
Yeah.
It's fine, isn't it?
It's close to the station and there's a convenience store right there, so shopping should be easy too.
This place is closer to the office than my home.
It's a very convenient apartment.
Why do we have to decide on your conditions?
Can he move in tomorrow?
Sure. If I have the deposit and take care of some paperwork,
then I'll be able to talk with the landlord.
Paperwork as in...?
At the very least, the lease contract.
I can wait for the guarantor's seal until tomorrow though.
And if that's the case...
Nanoka!
I thought you went home already.
And what are you gazing at by yourself?
I'm not gazing at anything in particular.
That's such a stupid answer.
Did something happen?
You've seemed so lifeless since this morning.
I'm fine.
It's just that I don't really feel like going home.
That's not "fine" at all, then!
Let's play games as much as we want!
Let's listen to CDs as much as we want!
Let's eat snacks as much as we want!
And we can also chit-chat as much as we want.
So cheer up, okay?
Yeah.
Hello Nanoka-chan.
Hello.
What's up with this room?
You should clean this place up.
Stop being so noisy.
I know, I will, so just be quiet, sis.
You never do it when no one tells you to.
Geez, Nanoka and I have something important to talk about.
It's a complicated issue that you'll never get, Onee.
Speaking of clothing, let me borrow that blue shirt.
fukuzatsu = complicated, fuku = clothing
You said you gave it to me and would never wear it again!
I changed my mind now. Hand it back.
That's so cheap!
Monster! Devil!
Are you sure it's okay?
Huh? You're moving tomorrow, right?
You'll be busy with this and that, right?
I'm sorry.
I'll make sure I pay you back.
Well, what happened?
It's nothing.
You wouldn't be running away in the middle of the night if it really was "nothing".
Don't say such cynical things.
But what you're doing is pretty much a night flight.
I guess so.
Thanks for your work.
What's up with him...?
One more time!
Okay.
That's cheap! Loser goes out!
Give it to me!
Onee, you're being so mean.
All right! All right!
This person is going to become a bride next year.
Can you believe it?
Really?
Yeah, pretty much.
Annual tribute...
She's...
She's...?
She's finally going to pay her annual tribute.
Japanese idiom for getting married
Have you girls found guys yet?
Well, it's the best time for "it".
"It" meaning pure love relationships.
Saying that while your marriage got arranged...
I just meant for relationship purposes.
There's much more to think about when it comes to marriage.
Don't you marry someone because you like him?
I like my fiancé, of course.
But just liking him isn't enough for this arrangement.
There are various constraints in reality.
And then you come to the point where you ask "is this really okay?"
Of course it'll be okay.
With you gone, this place will be so much more peaceful!
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Was that a call from her?
A-ah, yeah, sorry.
S-she said she's staying at a friend's house or something.
I see.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Hey, I'm...
I'll get it.
Hello, this is the Saeki's.
Hello.
Y-yo...
What's up?
I'll be staying at Futaba-chan's home tonight.
O-okay...
Dad just told me that.
And I also said that I'll be back before noon tomorrow.
But I think I'll stay here a bit longer, so...
I see.
-You know...
-I...
-Sorry.
-What?
Onii-chan.
You're not angry?
About what?
About me asking what you thought about me.
We'll be eating first, then.
O-okay.
I asked you such a weird question.
Ah, you did?
Yeah.
And then you said... I was weird.
Of course I didn't mean it.
But...
You're not weird and I'm not angry.
Really?
Yeah. That aside...
I should be the one apologizing for doing that to you...
Sorry, I know it's my fault.
I don't really care about that.
But...
Well, maybe I cared a little.
I'm sorry.
But, I don't really care that much about it.
I see.
I'm glad.
Same here.
To be able to talk with you.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, I...
Yeah?
No, nothing.
What is it?
I said nothing.
But I want to know.
Really, it's nothing.
Onii-chan.
I...
Maybe I'll call off staying over here tonight.
What are you talking about? I'm hanging up.
Okay.
See you.
The food's going to be gone!
Onee, you eat too much.
It's all right, I made these myself.
You won't be able to wear your wedding dress at this rate.
I'm still fine.
The say, "One second of negligence, one lifetime of obesity".
You too.
Nanoka?
What's the matter? Not hungry?
Or does the food look nasty?
What did you say?!
Of course not.
Then eat up! It's delicious.
That's right. Hey Futaba, grab some for her.
I know already!
But man, it's not like I'm saying no to you living alone.
I know this came out of the blue.
I'm sorry for saying this all of a sudden.
What are you not satisfied with?
Nothing like that.
That can't be!
Or else you wouldn't say you want to move out all of a sudden.
Well, I've been thinking about it for a while.
C'mon, just be sincere and tell me the truth.
Is there anything you're not content with about me?
Or did something happen between you and Nanoka?
No...
What's the matter?
I just felt like coming back.
So I came back.
What do you mean you're moving out?
Here.
Thanks.
Come in.
What's the matter?
Can we... sleep together?
I want to be with you.
At least for today.
Hey! Hold it for a second!
I am strange... after all.
Even though we're siblings, I...
I'm saying such selfish things.
It's not strange.
It's fine because we're siblings.
Stuff like this... in reality.
Then why are you moving out, Onii-chan?
You know.
I don't.
You should.
Let's make a promise, tonight's the last time.
We won't meet again.
Why?
Why are you saying this?
That's not right.
Things like "the last time"...
You're not going somewhere that far.
That's not right!
We're siblings.
Yeah, we're siblings.
I...
I always had something I wanted to say, but couldn't.
You remember when we rode on the ferris wheel?
Even though I wasn't really sure back then,
the truth is..
I was very happy that moment.
That's why at this rate, I...
a gentle dream
yasashii yume ga
やさしい夢が
calls the spring in my heart
sotto mune no haru wo yobi
そっと胸の春を呼び
and becomes a gentle breeze
yasashii kaze ni nari
やさしい風になり
that touches you then leaves
kimi ni furete satteyuku
君に触れて去ってゆく
in the small pot
chiisana potto ni wa
小さなポットには
are feelings of love
daisukina kimochi
大好きな気持ち
swaying softly
yurayura to
ゆらゆらと
that carry a sweet scent
ii kaori nosete
いい香りのせて
always waiting...
itsumo matteita
いつも待っていた
warming up this moment...
kono toki wo atatamete
この時をあたためて
things we understand because it's the two of us
futari dakara wakaru koto
ふたりだからわかる
are not just words
kotoba janakute
言葉じゃなくて
we just smile, we just hope
hohoemu dake negaudake
ほほえむだけ　願うだけ
to the quiet sky
shizukana sora e
しずかな空へ
we'll see each other again tomorrow...
ashita mo mata aeru yo ne
あしたもまた会えるよね
at the quiet sky
shizukana sora de
しずかな空で