Ah, I'm sorry. Ow...
A-are you all right?
Uh-huh, I just scraped my knee a little.
Okay?
J-just wait here a bit.
Thank you.
S-sure.
Spring thunder
Is this for me?
Yeah.
I thought your diet might be unbalanced from eating out too much.
I see.
Thanks.
Sure.
I'll...
It's fine, just sit down.
Brother...
Did it bother you?
The letter...
That's not it! This is...
I'm sorry, I broke the promise.
No, that's not it!
I won't ever come again.
That's not it.
This isn't what you think it is.
So, please stay here.
Brother, my arm hurts.
S-sorry.
I read your letter.
Yeah.
Try it on.
Come on, try it on for me.
Futaba.
Hey Futaba!
Why are you so out of it?
You're the one who invited us.
Oh yeah!
He's so cute!
You have bad taste.
No way...
Damn, he's such a handful.
Why am I the only one who has to work in this dim room?
If only Koshiro-san didn't take the day off.
If only he didn't take the day off.
Th-this is...!
So close.
Yes?
Thank god.
Thanks.
You want something to drink?
W-wait a second.
Ah...
I'll go buy something!
J-just wait a little bit.
Brother?
Do you want me to make you something?
Eh?
For dinner.
If you keep eating things like this, you'll really get sick.
But...
Let's go together!
I said don't move!
I'll go buy it, so write it down for me.
What do you want to eat?
Anything's fine.
How about seasoned rice?
Uh... Yeah, but...
I don't have a rice cooker...
Eh? Then you really don't cook at all by yourself?
I was thinking of buying one someday.
You have a frying pan, right?
Yeah.
Then...
What on earth am I doing?
Until a moment ago I was so depressed,
but now I'm all happy...
What did I leave the house for?
What was the past month for?
H-hi! Long time no see, Nanoka-chan.
H-hello.
Where's Koshiro?
He's out shopping right now.
I see.
Umm... Is there something you need?
Oh yeah, I left my pass here, when I slept over the other day.
Oh, don't mind me. I know where it is.
Are you going out with him?
Are you... going out with my brother?
That's right. You didn't know?
I guess he doesn't tell you about these things.
Is there something wrong with that?
I...
Sorry.
Kazuyoshi! You shouldn't stare at people like that!
I've fallen off...
I've totally fallen off...
What did Koshiro go to buy?
Ingredients for dinner.
Oh, are you going to make it, Nanoka-chan?
Yes.
I might stay for dinner too then.
Why is that?
Koshiro only offers me things he has on hand, so at least sometime...
Found it.
What's the meaning of this?
Please go home.
Eh?
Please go home!
Why?
Because you're in the way.
In the way?
I want to spend today with just my brother...
You know what?
How is it that I'm taking this from you,
who is only his younger sister?
I won't lose.
I won't lose to anyone over my feelings towards my brother!
Siblings can't fall in love with each other.
They can't even get married!
Do you understand that?
Your feelings are just temporary.
You're not able to see straight because there's too much blood rushing to your head.
You're probably only able to see your brother who is right in front of you.
But, I don't think such things will last very long.
Isn't it painful? It'll hurt when your feelings disappear.
He's your big brother!
I'll think about him for the rest of my life.
There is such a love, where you can think that.
The rest of your life?
So naive! Naive! The rest of your life, you say?
You can say it so easily. That's why you're called a child.
Old woman.
What do you think everyone else will say?
That won't matter.
It will matter.
Please go home!
You...
Go home!
Your parents will be saddened.
What a horrible face.
What horrible clothes.
I visit, worried about you and you're out shopping happily.
What the hell are you doing?
Why did you let her into your aparment?
You saw her?
I did.
I tried to make her leave by telling her we were going out,
but she chased me out instead.
What were you thinking of doing after this?
Why didn't you push her away?
What are you going to do now that you've got her hopes up?
I don't understand what you want to do at all, Koshiro.
I see that Nanoka-chan is also serious.
I'm sorry I said that you were the only one doing wrong.
But if that's the case, then it's more important for you to be firm!
I know...
You obviously don't!
It's fine already.
Wait! What's fine?
It's fine.
Have you thought about the future?
It doesn't matter to you!
Whether it matters is not the point!
How can I leave someone alone who is about to become knee-deep in misery?!
Don't judge who is miserable and who is not.
I won't ever involve myself in your affairs again.
I'm sorry I was so nosy from the beginning.
This is how it is.
Even though she seriously faced me like that,
I've finally lost her.
Welcome home!
I can still go back.
I'm home.
If she really is precious to me,
You're still soaking wet!
there is only one thing I can do...
Just say it to her...
That even if she does things like this for me it's only a nuisance.
Hurry up and understand.
It's no use telling her you don't need anything else.
Should we live together somewhere far away?
Eh?
Someplace where nobody knows us, so we can live as more than siblings?
Discarding everything else.
That's impossible for you, isn't it?
I love you more! More than Chidori-san.
I love you way more, brother!
Sorry...But... if you're going out with Chidori-san and you hate me,
I want you to tell me clearly.
Chidori and I are...
Tell her that's exactly right.
if I do that, everything will end.
That's exactly right.
Chidori and I are...
not going out.
She was just worried
about us siblings.
W-why can't siblings fall in love with each other?
I don't want to give up!
Stop it.
Don't say it.
That's just glossing over the problem.
I...
don't need anything else.
As long as I have you, I don't need anything else.
You understand, right?
It won't be the same anymore.
Yeah.
Are you really okay with that?
If you're fine with it, then I'm fine with it too.
I'm sorry... I'm sorry I fell in love with you.
That goes for the both of us.
Though there are other people we should apologize to.
We can't apologize, can we?
Yeah.
Hello? Is this Nanoka?
No, it's me.
It's already late. I'll let her stay at my place.
Yeah, it's fine.
She doesn't have school tomorrow.
Yeah.
Okay, don't worry about it.
Bye.
yasashii yume ga
a gentle dream
sotto mune no haru wo yobi
calls the spring in my heart
yasashii kaze ni nari
and becomes a gentle breeze
kimi ni furete satteyuku
that touches you then leaves
chiisana potto ni wa
in the small pot
daisukina kimochi
are feelings of love
yurayura to
swaying softly
ii kaori nosete
that carry a sweet scent
itsumo matteita
always waiting...
kono toki wo atatamete
warming up this moment...
futari dakara wakaru koto
things we understand because it's the two of us
kotoba janakute
are not just words
hohoemu dake negaudake
we just smile, we just hope
shizukana sora e
to the quiet sky
ashita mo mata aeru yo ne
we'll see each other again tomorrow...
at the quiet sky
shizukana sora de
Serial Taige Preview
Chidori goes
With Koshiro-san gone, having Chidori-san harass me feels nice.
But I want to stick to teenagers! This is my goal!
Punishment: No role in the next episode!
Oh, please at least one scene.