anime.fin
presents
hajimete no kimochi
my first feelings
shonbori no mune ni
upon my downhearted chest
source
Ultima
sotto nagerareta hidamarine
a sunny ray of light was gently thrown
translation
minidora07
encode
maxx-
hitori aruiteta
walking alone...
sora miageta toki
when I looked up at the sky,
typeset & karaoke
maxx-
haru ga soko ni kiteta
spring was near,
misetekureta
it showed me
timing
MEdo-kun
kowareru omoiwa
these trembling feelings are
maichiru hanabirane
fluttering petals,
sukininatte iino
is it okay for me to fall in love?
soretomo
or will...
tamerau kokoro ga
my hesitating heart
bureiki kakerukedo
put on my brakes,
kurushikute
it's so painful
ikiga tomarisou desu
I can't breathe
thanks to
anime-station
#anime.fin @ chatsociety.net
Wind flower
I thought about moving out of the house.
I love you, brother.
She's cute.
Honestly, she's a lot of trouble, but I can't leave her alone.
Where?
I was feeling constrained by forcing myself to think that she is my younger sister.
That guy with the black jersey.
Eh, where?
Isn't he cute?
I can't tell; he's too far away.
Didn't he just look this way?
You don't mean that second year, do you?
He's famous for having a girlfriend who is in college.
Eh!? What a bummer.
Hey, what are you girls doing?
Teacher.
You girls look like you're bored.
Not really... umm...
Ah! I can't believe this! What's the meaning of this?
We should've just made an excuse and ran away.
He had that look on his face when he came to us, so it was already too late.
I'm sorry. It's because I was too slow.
Why are you apologizing Nanoka?
It's because Yama-chan is a slave driver.
Yeah.
Do you think this is good enough?
Yeah, good job.
Okay, mission complete!
Hey, don't we have to put these books over here in order?
Hey Nanoka, it's fine. Let's go home.
How much do you plan on spoiling Yama-chan?
Spoil him?
You're so damn honest!
We don't have to do that much.
But I guess that seriousness is Nanoka's good point.
I'll go get our stuff.
Wait for us at the front gate.
Okay. I'll go tell the teacher that we have finished cleaning.
Don't get caught again!
Be careful!
I'm not that serious...
Nanoka!
Yes?
The bath is free! Hurry up and take a bath.
Yeah, I'll be there in a second.
I'm home.
Welcome home. You're early.
Yeah.
What the heck is this?
You should at least clean it up a little.
Don't spread out cookie crumbs on top of the newspaper.
But they keep crumbling.
If you keep munching on too many snacks, you're going to turn into a pig.
Pig?
Oink, oink.
No I won't!
Just kidding.
Hurry and clean it up.
No! I won't, I won't I won't become a pig!
I'll do that for you Nanoka, so hurry and take your bath!
Oh shut up!
Oh, Dad...
Hey, Dad?
I'm sorry, Dad.
Mom... Nanoka has finally entered her rebellious phase...
This little girl will take another step towards adulthood in this way...
Dad?
Why do you put on the innocent face in front of Dad?
Don't force yourself.
I'm not forcing myself!
How shocking... even my brother...
Why do people always think of me like that?
Brother's at work, huh?
It's boring...
To Nanoka
I'm going to eat together
with Yamada-san and company.
Your lunch is the fried-rice
pack in the freezer.
Heat it up and eat it.
Dad
Oh, you're there.
Yeah.
Were you still sleeping? It's past noon already.
What? What is it?
Hey, was there an envelope on the table or somewhere?
Just a minute.
Hello? The white big one?
Did you find it? The one with my company's name?
I'm sorry, but could you bring that over?
You said never to go to your work place.
Did I ever say that?
Yeah, you did.
Fine. I'm sorry I relied on you.
It's not like I can't go out. I'll come home and get it.
If you really need me to, then I can bring it for you.
Why can I only say it like that?
Nobody wants an uncute younger sister like me.
Oh, so sorry.
Did you rush here? I just needed you to bring it by four.
Was this the one?
Yeah. You saved me. Thanks a lot.
Yeah.
Well, I'll give you some money. Go shop around before you go home.
Umm... Do you think you'll finish late today?
Hmm?
I want to go home together.
It's fine if you can't.
No... I didn't say I couldn't... but...
Saeki-kun, could you come for a minute?
Yes.
Then why don't you take a seat around here and wait for me.
Sorry for making you wait.
As for the membership, the members enter after we've given them a strict examination,
so there aren't any suspicious people...
Hello.
Long time no see.
Is coffee okay?
Thank you very much.
What a lousy brother, leaving his sister like this.
That's not true.
Umm... Do you mind if I stay here?
It's fine.
But isn't it boring for you to be here?
Why don't you wait for your brother downstairs in the cafe?
It's all right. I'll wait here.
All right. Well, I'm going to go out for a while, so take your time.
Yes.
You must have been bored.
No.
What is it?
I just thought you were really different from usual,
different from when you're at home.
Well of course I'd be different at work and at home.
Brother, even though I don't really think so,
my friends at school say I'm too serious.
Since when? You're so lazy.
I'm not! I'm not!
Which is it?
Right. You're right.
I'm a liar. I put on a facade.
Just like you said, even though I'm not.
Sorry. It's my fault. I said too much.
Everyone does that at some time.
Well, my different personalities at work and home must seem like a very dishonest, adult thing to do.
That's not true.
You were cool!
Then you should just leave it at that.
I don't care whether you're serious or lazy.
You call people like me liars.
No you aren't!
If you found out the truth about me, you'd probably hate me.
What? You say it as if you're so confident that you're well-liked!
Hey!
Idiot! Hey!
Don't pull me!
Do you have to swing like that?
I had completely forgotten
the fact that I was even thinking of leaving home.
I wished she wasn't my younger sister at all.
I thought about such things...
Good morning, brother.
What is it?
Is something the matter?
Ah... No, it's nothing.
Good morning, dad.
Good morning, Nanoka.
What? You still haven't left?
Jeez...
Stop it.
No.
I said stop.
No!
Oh, good morning.
Hello.
Good morning.
It's so nice that you guys get along so well.
My kids are always fighting with each other since their ages are so close.
Eww, don't do that. Stop it!
It's not. It's alright.
What is?
Stop it...
Hey brother.
I want to go out and play somewhere.
Go.
I want to go with you, brother.
Why?
Just because.
I'm too lazy, so no.
Recently, we've only gone on neighborhood strolls and grocery shopping.
Isn't that enough?
It's not.
We went to Hakone over summer vacation.
I want to go to a proper place.
Let's go somewhere during the next holiday.
It's a promise, brother!
I don't want to think about unnecessary things for now.
I saw it!
You and Nanoka-chan walking together last night.
Nanoka-chan is so cute!
I can see how you can get so wrapped up in taking care of her.
What are you saying?
If someone who doesn't know anything sees you two,
it might seem like you guys have that  kind of a relationship.
Odagiri, come here for a second!
What is it?
Midori-sama will pour for you!
No thank you!
I know that I have to do something about it.
Drink if you're a man!
If you enter his room without his permission,
he'll get angry.
She's my younger sister.
Without a doubt, my...
Why?
Is she asleep?
Besides that... Why is she...?
Geez... You want me to jump on you?
What are you doing?
You'll catch a cold.
Yeah.
Aren't you going to get angry?
Nothing.
Do you want to sleep together?
Sorry, just kidding.
I'm going to sleep now, so go back to your own room.
Brother... what do you think of me?
You know how I feel, right?
I...
...brother...
Don't say it!
love you.
You know that right?
Don't say anymore!
Brother!
Don't say it.
You love me like a sister would love her brother.
No!
Saying that you love your sibling like that...
That's not what I want to say...!
Something's wrong with you.
No!
yasashii yume ga
a gentle dream
sotto mune no haru wo yobi
calls the spring in my heart
yasashii kaze ni nari
and becomes a gentle breeze
kimi ni furete satteyuku
that touches you then leaves
chiisana potto ni wa
in the small pot
daisukina kimochi
are feelings of love
yurayura to
swaying softly
ii kaori nosete
that carry a sweet scent
itsumo matteita
always waiting...
kono toki wo atatamete
warming up this moment...
futari dakara wakaru koto
things we understand because it's the two of us
kotoba janakute
are not just words
hohoemu dake negaudake
we just smile, we just hope
shizukana sora e
to the quiet sky
ashita mo mata aeru yo ne
we'll see each other again tomorrow...
at the quiet sky
shizukana sora de
Serial Taige Preview
Chidori goes
Dearest, it seems that Nanoka is in her rebellious phase, and I am all alone.
I don't care about Koshiro, but I definitely want to at least secure my daughter's heart.
That is what I, Zenzou, am feeling in the Autumn of my 51st year.
Punishment of the Human Rocket!