I feel this way for the first time.
hajimete no kimochi
はじめての気持ち
A ray of sunshine
shonbori no mune ni
しょんぼりの胸に
was suddenly cast into my saddened heart.
potto nagerareta hidamarine
ぽっと投げられた陽だまりね
Walking alone,
hitori aruiteta
ひとり歩いてた
I looked up at the sky,
sora miageta toki
空みあげた時
and saw spring was near.
haru ga soko ni kiteta
春がそこに来てた
It showed me
misetekureta
見せてくれた
these trembling feelings are
kogareru omoiwa
焦がれる想いは
like whirling petals.
maichiru hanabirane
舞い散る花びらね
Is it okay for me to fall in love?
sukininatte iino
好きになっていいの？
Or...
soretomo
それとも
My hesitating heart
tamerau kokoro ga
ためらう心が
puts on the brakes.
bureiki kakerukedo
ブレーキかけるけど
It’s so painful,
kurushikute
苦しくて
I can’t breathe.
ikiga tomarisou desu
息が止まりそうです
Gentle Breeze
I can't sleep...
Why do I...
...keep thinking about her?
Now that I think about it...
When I was really little,
there were nights when I couldn't get to sleep.
At times like that...
Mom would soothe me by patting my head.
That's weird...
I swear it was somewhere in here...
Ow!
Yeah...
When I was a little kid, without him...
There's nothing we can do.
You're the one who forgot it.
First thing tomorrow morning, we'll ask the bus company. All right?
What a troublesome child you are.
Just like my mom did for me that day,
if I could give something to her,
maybe this feeling would go away.
Is what I found myself thinking.
Maybe I'm the child.
Or is she the innocent child?
Or...
What do you want?!
How cute!
Is this yours, Onii-chan?
Don't just come into my room like that!
How surprising!
You treasure such a cute teddy bear?
It's not that I'm treasuring it.
Yes you are!
You washed it and cleaned it, right?
No, that wasn't... what I...
But, that way of drying isn't nice!
Right?
If you want it, I'll give it to you.
But...
My mom made it for me when I was a kid.
It doesn't really make a difference if you have it.
I'll give it to you.
Wait a second!
Here!
This one's mine.
Mom made one for made it for me too.
You can have it.
I'll keep this one,
so take care of that one, Onii-chan.
I don't want this.
No! Take care of it!
Don't bully it!
She is definitely a child...
...so I think.
I'd like to think but...
You came during third period?
When I woke up, the morning show was over.
I thought I should have just come in the afternoon, at first.
You should've just taken the day off.
But you know...
I actually benefited from coming late!
I saw this really cute guy on the train!
What kind?
He was tall, and fair skinned
with really nice hair and really long eye lashes.
He was probably a high school student!
He was wearing a school uniform!
At such an hour?
Yeah! That's the point!
The point?
I was so late,  but he was on the same train car
on the same train at the same time!
Don't you think it's fate?
Yeah, sort of!
Isn't it? Isn't it? I feel a romance coming on!
Romance...?
Loser buys drinks!
Fine, because I'm going to win.
Nanoka?
Was it?
Yeah. Thanks!
You're a life saver.
Are you okay?
You don't look so well.
I'm fine.
Marriage
Consulting
Huh?
Koshiro, you're taking tomorrow off too?
Yeah, it's a compensatory day off from last week.
Isn't Wakanai-san's arranged marriage meeting tomorrow?
Is it?
Yeah, it is!
Shoot, I completely forgot about it.
I'll come after lunch.
It's okay.
You can take the day off.
I'll go in your place.
That's not okay!
Isn't he extremely shy in front of strangers?
So that he won't get nervous, we have to start from that meeting room,
then go to a nearby cafe, then go to a European restaurant...
I can't leave such an important job
to someone who's been in a daze all the time lately.
See, there you go lost in thought again.
Anyway, go get some rest tomorrow!
Yeah...
That cute guy you were talking about earlier,
what school does he go to?
I wish I could've found that out...
I've never seen his uniform before.
Maybe it's the all-boys school that was established last year.
But if he was on the same train as you today
there's a chance you could see him again, right?
I want to see what he looks like too!
What? What's wrong?
What should I do?
It's that blonde guy?
Oh my god! Can I believe in fate?
He's the guy from this morning?!
you think he's good-looking too right?
What should I do?
Wait a minute!
I want to take a better look at him!
Nanoka...
Did you see that?
It was Tamaki, right? He was kissing Tamaki, right?
Yeah...
That girl! She said she wasn't interested!
I'll make her spill it all out tomorrow!
I'm home.
You...
Welcome home.
You're early.
What's wrong?
What's that medicine for?
Oh, it's nothing.
Just a pain reliever.
I'm going to go lie down in my room.
Hey, is Nanoka all right?
She was probably up late yesterday or something.
Nanoka...
Please knock
Nanoka
It looks like the beginning of the rainy season.
The weather in the Kantou region isn't very clear.
There won't be any rain from tonight to tomorrow morning, but
it will most likely rain tomorrow afternoon.
Please don't forget to bring your umbrella when you go out.
Next, tomorrow's weather for each area on Tokyo.
It will be cloudy followed by rain in Tokyo city.
Probability of precipitation in the morning is 60%
In the afternoon it will be 70%...
Aren't you hungry?
Where are you going at this hour?
A walk.
What are you saying? You're not feeling well, right?
I just have really bad menstrual cramps.
First time in three months?
Is that alright?
The doctor told me it's common for girls my age.
I'm sorry for making you worry even though I'm not really sick.
It's alright.
Do you want to go to the convenience store on the way back?
Are you all right? Don't force yourself!
Onii-chan, you're over-exaggerating.
I'm fine.
Today,
I saw my friend kissing a guy.
I wonder if I'm going to kiss someone someday?
I'm going to have you explain everything about yesterday!
I have nothing to explain.
Where did you meet him?
In junior high. We went to the same cram school.
Cram school?
That's something that is unrelated to me!
Ouch!
I said something weird last night...
Onii-chan's probably used to kissing.
He's an adult.
When will I become an adult?
Isn't there any good love rolling around?
What?
Is that strange?
Not really.
Right?
Crap!
Shit...
It'll probably stop soon.
When you're in love, even boring things make your heart jump!
That's what makes it really fun!
Yeah!
Oh no... it's gotten worse.
Onii-chan...
Onii-chan!
I'm home.
Did you come to pick me up?
No way.
I was on my way to the store because I ran out of tobacco.
It's true! I only brought one umbrella too!
Yeah.
I know.
Are you all right?
Your stomach ache?
What are you smiling about?
Nothing.
Whatever.
Weirdo.
A gentle dream
yasashii yume ga
やさしい夢が
calls the spring in my heart
sotto mune no haru wo yobi
そっと胸の春を呼び
and becomes a gentle breeze
yasashii kaze ni nari
やさしい風になり
that touches you, then leaves.
kimi ni furete satteyuku
君に触れて去ってゆく
In the small pot
chiisana potto ni wa
小さなポットには
are feelings of love
daisukina kimochi
大好きな気持ち
swaying softly.
yurayura to
ゆらゆらと
They carry a sweet scent,
ii kaori nosete
いい香りのせて
always waiting,
itsumo matteita
いつも待っていた
warming up this moment.
kono toki wo atatamete
この時をあたためて
We understand each other
futari dakara wakaru koto
ふたりだからわかる
without words.
kotoba janakute
言葉じゃなくて
We just smile and hope
hohoemu dake negaudake
ほほえむだけ　願うだけ
to the peaceful sky.
shizukana sora e
しずかな空へ
Hope that we’ll see each other again tomorrow
ashita mo mata aeru yo ne
あしたもまた会えるよね
to the peaceful sky.
shizukana sora de
しずかな空で