I feel this way for the first time.
hajimete no kimochi
はじめての気持ち
A ray of sunshine
shonbori no mune ni
しょんぼりの胸に
was suddenly cast into my saddened heart.
potto nagerareta hidamarine
ぽっと投げられた陽だまりね
Walking alone,
hitori aruiteta
ひとり歩いてた
I looked up at the sky,
sora miageta toki
空みあげた時
and saw spring was near.
haru ga soko ni kiteta
春がそこに来てた
It showed me
misetekureta
見せてくれた
these trembling feelings are
kogareru omoiwa
焦がれる想いは
like whirling petals.
maichiru hanabirane
舞い散る花びらね
Is it okay for me to fall in love?
sukininatte iino
好きになっていいの？
Or...
soretomo
それとも
My hesitating heart
tamerau kokoro ga
ためらう心が
puts on the brakes.
bureiki kakerukedo
ブレーキかけるけど
It’s so painful,
kurushikute
苦しくて
I can’t breathe.
ikiga tomarisou desu
息が止まりそうです
Spring Blues
The town I was born in.
The house I was born in.
My father and Onii-chan.
It's like I just met them for the first time,
but they're very nostalgic people.
Good morning, Onii-chan!
Onii-chan!
Onii-chan, wait up!
I'm home.
Welcome back, Onii-chan.
Isn't this nitsuke/stew delicious?
Yeah.
My mother taught me how to make it.
Onii-chan!
Eh?
Let's go to the amusement park together again!
Somehow, everything looks like it's sparkling.
A younger sister...?
Good morning, Onii-chan!
Umm...
What do you usually do for lunch?
I made you lunch today.
If it's all right with you, would you take it?
Onii-chan?
Onii-chan!
Onii-chan...
Eh? And then?
He said he was anemic...
Is he sickly?
He's been looking kind of pale lately.
Hmm...
I want to...
become...
closer to...
my brother.
You don't get along with him?
That's not it, but...
But it feels so awkward.
It can't be helped if he's twelve years older than you.
But... more...
since we're siblings after all.
The fire of envy is burning wildly within my heart...
Thanks for the meal!
That idiot...!
Well, I guess I'll head home.
Good work.
You should hurry up and go home early too.
Isn't your cute little sister waiting?
That's why I don't want to...
Have her make you a meal full of love!
Like the bento from lunch!
Shut up!
There's nothing to worry about!
I'll take care of your membership entrance!
Umm, I'm not interested...
You are...
Glasses...
Glasses...?
Onii-chan!
You!
I came to visit.
So she says.
Why don't we all go out and eat together?
Hurry and finish up your work.
Dad said he would be late today so we should go out and eat.
Onii-chan, what would you like to eat...
Hey! Koushiro!
Idiot! Why did you come all the way here?!
Because...
Listen, I don't want you to ever come to my office again!
Understand?
Onii-chan...
Did I...
Hey, Onii-chan...
And stop calling me Onii-chan!
Then...
Then what should I call you?
Hey...
It was a chance to become close to a female high school student lawfully.
He was such a jerk!
He went off to work early by himself.
Didn't you say you wanted to be closer yesterday?
I'm so disappointed.
To be honest,
I want to play with him and have him help me with homework...
It wasn't supposed to be like this.
Aren't most siblings like that?
All I do is fight with my older sister.
I didn't think he was so mean!
I'm never going to call my brother "Onii-chan" again!
Now, now.
Then why don't we go have some fun after school,
and let out all our feelings!
Okay?
Yeah!
Poor girl.
She visited you because she wanted to be closer to you.
That attitude was uncalled for, wasn't it?
Shut up! I know that already.
Then what?
What do you not like about her?
It's nothing.
It's not like I dislike her.
When she's in front of me,
it just makes me want to run away.
What's wrong with you?
Did you go crazy after you got your heart broken?
I forgot...
I forgot about it... completely.
Damn it!
It's so sweet! This is so good!
Isn't it, isn't it?
Chocolate caramel ice cream is definitely the best!
Yeah!
Nanoka, you don't know much about the stores around here, right?
Let's go shopping together next time.
I'll show you around!
Yeah!
Hey, Futaba-chan!
What's up?
You're eating that again?
You sure love the ice cream from this place.
She went to the same junior high as me.
I'm Tamaki Youko from class four. Nice to meet you.
I'm Kohinata Nanoka. Nice to meet you too.
Hey, I'm actually going to go karaoke with my friends,
so would you guys want to come along too?
I'm home.
What are you doing?
Nanoka said...
on the phone that she's going to be late.
What?
She contacted you, so what's the problem.
You idiot!
Right now, Nanoka could be surrounded by strange men and might get kidnapped!
If something like that happens...
I... I'll...
You're overreacting.
Ah! I sang a lot!
It was so much fun!
I feel so refreshed.
I know, right?
It's gotten kind of late, huh?
Are you okay, Nanoka?
I called them just in case.
Let's go again next time!
Yeah!
I'll see you tomorrow, then.
See you! Bye!
Try to make up with your brother.
This is the Saeki residence.
This is Nanoka.
Are you stupid?!
What have you been doing until this hour?
Um... no...
Where are you right now?
At the public phone outside the park.
Why did you walk through there?
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Don't you know there are many perverts around there?
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
Watch out for molesters!
If you see a
suspicious person, call 110
I got it!
I was just going to tell you I'm heading home right now!
Bye!
Hey! Hello?
What's with him?!
He's so arrogant!
I was feeling down...
I know now...
That time...
I didn't know why you cried that time, but...
thanks to that, I didn't have to cry.
Even if I remember about the guy I used to like,
I'm all right now.
But...
Why does it have to be like this?
Get on.
No thanks.
Who do you think I came out here for?
Hurry up and get on.
Onii-chan, you just did that on your own!
Fine...
Call me whatever you wish.
Dad is worried about you,
let's hurry up and go home.
We're leaving.
Okay.
Onii-chan?
What?
Nothing...
As for me,
I was getting irritated from still feeling uncomfortable.
She's my younger sister.
So this is fine.
This is normal, and ordinary.
I continued pedaling as if to tell myself that.
A gentle dream
yasashii yume ga
やさしい夢が
calls the spring in my heart
sotto mune no haru wo yobi
そっと胸の春を呼び
and becomes a gentle breeze
yasashii kaze ni nari
やさしい風になり
that touches you, then leaves.
kimi ni furete satteyuku
君に触れて去ってゆく
In the small pot
chiisana potto ni wa
小さなポットには
are feelings of love
daisukina kimochi
大好きな気持ち
swaying softly.
yurayura to
ゆらゆらと
They carry a sweet scent,
ii kaori nosete
いい香りのせて
always waiting,
itsumo matteita
いつも待っていた
warming up this moment.
kono toki wo atatamete
この時をあたためて
We understand each other
futari dakara wakaru koto
ふたりだからわかる
without words.
kotoba janakute
言葉じゃなくて
We just smile and hope
hohoemu dake negaudake
ほほえむだけ　願うだけ
to the peaceful sky.
shizukana sora e
しずかな空へ
Hope that we’ll see each other again tomorrow
ashita mo mata aeru yo ne
あしたもまた会えるよね
to the peaceful sky.
shizukana sora de
しずかな空で