my first feelings
hajimete no kimochi
はじめての気持ち
upon my downhearted chest
shonbori no mune ni
しょんぼりの胸に
a sunny ray of light was gently thrown
potto nagerareta hidamarine
ぽっと投げられた陽だまりね
walking alone...
hitori aruiteta
ひとり歩いてた
when I looked up at the sky,
sora miageta toki
空みあげた時
spring was near,
haru ga soko ni kiteta
春がそこに来てた
it showed me
misetekureta
見せてくれた
these trembling feelings are
kogareru omoiwa
焦がれる想いは
fluttering petals,
maichiru hanabirane
舞い散る花びらね
is it okay for me to fall in love?
sukininatte iino
好きになっていいの？
or will...
soretomo
それとも
my hesitating heart
tamerau kokoro ga
ためらう心が
put on my brakes,
bureiki kakerukedo
ブレーキかけるけど
it's so painful
kurushikute
苦しくて
I can't breathe
ikiga tomarisou desu
息が止まりそうです
Dew frost
The conference members are basically selected after we do a strict examination.
There really aren't any suspicious people, so to say...
or any people with problems.
If there are any conflicts between two members,
we'll take responsibility...
It was a job I just chose to do,
because employment opportunities were limited for a third-class university graduate.
Or so I thought.
Or I was trying to make myself think.
In truth, I wanted to experience people's happiness,
I wanted to experience people's sadness.
I wanted to place myself somewhere where people encounter and separate.
If I kept doing that, I thought I'd be able to do the same someday...
From now on, I want you to help me with the house chores more often than before, okay?
I feel kind of bad doing this to you since there's such a large age difference.
What's wrong? You don't seem too happy.
You're finally going to be a big brother...
Oh, isn't it almost time?
One more month.
You're a big brother now, aren't you, Ko-chan?
Yes! We did it, Koshiro!
Congratulations, it's a girl.
It was a kind of a happy, yet scary, feeling.
But that was the only time I had that feeling.
I'm home.
What is it?
What do you want?!
Hey, wait...
My, my, what's going on?
Come on, what's the matter?
Ugh... Not again.
Now, now, don't cry, don't cry.
It's not my fault!
Here.
Which is it?!
You aren't bullying her while we're out, are you?
Nanoka seems to be afraid of you!
Who cares!
You're so helpless.
It wasn't me!
That's not it.
Will you come to the other room?
It's not that we're quarreling with each other,
or we got into a big fight or anything.
It's just...
We thought we should live separately before that happens.
That's right.
We're sorry that we have to make you go through some sad times.
We're really sorry about that.
Even though we'll be living apart,
it doesn't mean I'll stop being your mother,
or that she's no longer your sister.
We're still family.
Yeah.
I thought divorces weren't such peaceful things in my mind as a child, but...
I could tell that mom and dad were trying to separate peacefully for me.
Well, we should get going.
Koshiro, keep an eye on the house for me.
Okay.
Bye now.
Don't look so sulky forever.
Be more honest with yourself, okay?
Yeah.
You can come any time.
Good work.
What, you've been going home early lately.
What?
He must want to see Nanoka-san as soon as possible.
I'm so envious!
No way. He's not you.
I love you, Onii-chan.
Why is it that I even headed there?
Without even understanding it myself,
I was walking in the town that she grew up in without me knowing.
My!
So you finally came to my house.
How did you know?
Of course I'd know!
It's you, Koshiro!
I thought you would've forgotten my face.
Did you forget my face?
See? Even if we haven't seen each other for years, that's how it is between a parent and child.
And?
What's the matter?
Did something happen?
Why?
You just suddenly came. There must be some reason, isn't there?
No reason. I just felt like it.
Really?
From when she was a child...
Oh.
She just loves bears.
She really is your younger sister, that kid.
You exchanged dolls, I heard.
Nanoka was talking about it so happily when she came back during summer vacation.
Why did you send her over to our house?
When you took her with you when you got divorced,
why would you suddenly bring her back to dad?
Because she got into a high school near your house.
Are you serious?
I'd feel bad if she had to commute two hours each way every day.
What? What's the matter?
It's nothing.
What? did you come all the way over just to sulk?
What are you doing?
Here, come with me.
What is it?
How many years has it been since I last cut your hair?
I forgot.
You wouldn't let me cut it much after you became a big brother.
What were you getting all worked up about?
Onii-chan.
What?
She isn't bothering you?
Saying, Onii-chan, Onii-chan, Onii-chan...
How do you know?
Well, you see...
I wonder what Onii-chan is like?
I want to meet him soon.
I wonder if he'll help me with studying.
Oh, nothing, nothing at all.
He will help you, I'm sure, with your studies.
Yeah!
She probably really wanted to live with you guys... or just you.
Oh...
So take good care of her, okay?
Zenzou-san is no good when you really need him.
Okay...
What? You'd better make sure you take care of things.
You're a big brother, aren't you?
Hey.
What would you do if I made her unhappy?
What?
If I somehow made her unhappy,
what would you do?
If such a thing happened,
I wouldn't let you get away with it.
Of course.
Weird kid.
You still don't seem to be very honest with yourself.
Really?
It means you haven't grown up at all.
You'd better be stronger.
It's the most difficult phase
at that age.
Why don't you stay a little longer, since its been a while?
How can I?
I have work tomorrow too.
You have to eat properly.
Okay.
Oh yes. Nanoka's flavoring is usually a little too strong,
so tell her to be careful.
Yeah, I got it.
And don't give her too much allowance.
I wouldn't give her any even if she begged.
And tell her not to stay up too late.
I got it already. I'll be late for my train.
But...
I know.
I understand.
Thank you, Koshiro.
Okay, bye.
Get along with her, okay?
Yeah.
I'm back.
Welcome home, Onii-chan.
I'm... home.
Want some?
Okay.
You're not going to cry?
Eh?
No, nothing.
Hey, Onii-chan?
Where did you go today?
Somewhere.
What?
Just for a walk.
To where?
Somewhere.
You should've taken me too.
I'm fine with being Onii-chan.
I'm fine with just being close to each other as siblings.
If that's the role that I was given,
I'll do what I must.
So...
Don't you have to get up early tomorrow?
Yeah.
But you too, Onii-chan.
I'll take a smoke and then go to sleep.
So go to sleep.
Okay.
I'll do it.
Good night then.
Yeah.
So don't say that you love me.
a gentle dream
yasashii yume ga
やさしい夢が
calls the spring in my heart
sotto mune no haru wo yobi
そっと胸の春を呼び
and becomes a gentle breeze
yasashii kaze ni nari
やさしい風になり
that touches you then leaves
kimi ni furete satteyuku
君に触れて去ってゆく
in the small pot
chiisana potto ni wa
小さなポットには
are feelings of love
daisukina kimochi
大好きな気持ち
swaying softly
yurayura to
ゆらゆらと
that carry a sweet scent
ii kaori nosete
いい香りのせて
always waiting...
itsumo matteita
いつも待っていた
warming up this moment...
kono toki wo atatamete
この時をあたためて
things we understand because it's the two of us
futari dakara wakaru koto
ふたりだからわかる
are not just words
kotoba janakute
言葉じゃなくて
we just smile, we just hope
hohoemu dake negaudake
ほほえむだけ　願うだけ
to the quiet sky
shizukana sora e
しずかな空へ
we'll see each other again tomorrow...
ashita mo mata aeru yo ne
あしたもまた会えるよね
at the quiet sky
shizukana sora de
しずかな空で