I feel this way for the first time.
hajimete no kimochi
はじめての気持ち
A ray of sunshine
shonbori no mune ni
しょんぼりの胸に
was suddenly cast into my saddened heart.
potto nagerareta hidamarine
ぽっと投げられた陽だまりね
Walking alone,
hitori aruiteta
ひとり歩いてた
I looked up at the sky,
sora miageta toki
空みあげた時
and saw spring was near.
haru ga soko ni kiteta
春がそこに来てた
It showed me
misetekureta
見せてくれた
these trembling feelings are
kogareru omoiwa
焦がれる想いは
like whirling petals.
maichiru hanabirane
舞い散る花びらね
Is it okay for me to fall in love?
sukininatte iino
好きになっていいの？
Or...
soretomo
それとも
My hesitating heart
tamerau kokoro ga
ためらう心が
puts on the brakes.
bureiki kakerukedo
ブレーキかけるけど
It’s so painful,
kurushikute
苦しくて
I can’t breathe.
ikiga tomarisou desu
息が止まりそうです
Evening Shower
Hey.
Are you all right?
What?
Your face.
It's terrible!
Did you get a good rest on your day off?
Yeah.
You look so out of it to me.
That's not true.
You should fix yourself up for the event, at least.
I know.
Are you still brooding over it?
Your break-up?
No way.
Well, it's fine then.
In truth,
Machida Marriage Consulting
Party Meeting Room
I don't have any regrets now about getting dumped.
Koshiro, have you ever loved anyone from the bottom of your heart?
No.
I'm terrible at getting the gist of things.
You don't look that way.
...and then I fell down.
Odagiri!
Yes?
...but usually I'm pretty calm.
What should we do about today's after-party?
The chief said it's on him.
Really? Yes!
Of course I'm in!
I made a promise today so I'll be leaving first.
Promise?
A movie. I'm watching a movie.
Is it with Nanoka-san?
What's your point?
I can't help it. She forced me to promise her.
I'd love to go with you!
Shut up! You just go and drink with the chief!
Koshiro,
the other day, after we had a meeting here, weren't you flirting with a high school girl?
Was that...?
Flirting?!
With a high school girl?
I-I-Idiot! N-No!
That was...
That was Nanoka, wasn't it?
Why didn't you just say she was your sister in the first place?
Odagiri, help me carry these.
Yes.
What did you mean by, "flirting with Nanoka"?
No idea.
I don't really get it either.
Why?
Don't stare at me like it's that unusual.
But, why?
You had a beard this morning!
We have to look clean for our events, or we'll get scolded.
Look clean?
Is it weird?
You look cool!
But it looks painful!
What are you saying...?
This movie is...
Don't get so close!
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
Why are you spacing out?
No reason.
Give me your student ID.
Oh, yeah.
What's wrong?
I'll go buy the tickets.
What is he thinking, making you come home all alone at this hour?
He said, "it doesn't matter; just go home first".
That guy is hopeless.
He went off somewhere right after the movie ended.
Where did that bum go?
I don't know. He didn't say anything.
Hey.
Your uniform's going to get wrinkled.
I don't care.
So?
About earlier.
That was my younger sister.
I don't think I ever told you, but...
she's my younger sister whom I've been living apart from until now.
You know my parents are divorced, right?
She's been with my mom the whole time.
We started living together this spring because her high school is nearby.
That's it?
Is that really all?
Yeah.
What?
You said you had something to tell me, so I was wondering what it could be.
It's not a laughing matter!
I didn't want you to think I started going after high school girls since getting dumped.
I was worried for nothing.
It's just so like you, to be worried about appearances while dating high school girls.
Well, I'm sorry.
I'll never come again.
Dinner...
Have you eaten yet?
Suddenly, a foolish thought passed through my mind.
"That's right; it's been three months since I last had sex".
But it's fine, because you can drink!
That's not true.
It is! You're way stronger than me!
Isn't it good?
It's my favorite restaurant.
Yeah.
I come here often by myself.
What are you saying, stupid?
I'm not stupid. I'm serious.
I don't believe you!
I don't joke around about things like that.
How about Sachiko-chan?
She's just a friend.
No way!
I'm serious!
You...
How's work been lately?
Why?
You used to always tell me that you wanted to quit.
You still remember?
Who could forget after listening to you complain so much?
Going by your half-hearted replies, I thought you weren't listening.
That's not true.
So, how's your job?
The same as always, I guess.
I see.
And you?
Was there an event today?
Yeah.
Or did you shave your beard because your high school girlfriend told you to?
I told you, she's...
What is it?
Nothing.
What?
I was wondering if any taxis would come this way.
If you go a little further you'll reach the main street.
It'll be easier to find one there.
I'm moving next month.
I'm quitting my job, too.
Although that's a little later on.
I see.
By the way, my boyfriend is coming now.
Yeah.
What?
He's a very good person.
I see.
Best of luck to you, Koshiro.
Really.
Good night.
"What should we do afterwards?"
I'm glad I didn't say anything stupid like that.
I'm really glad.
Don't stay up too late!
Yes.
I wasn't going out with her just for the sex.
Koshiro, have you ever loved anyone from the bottom of your heart?
But I don't think it's bad.
Is it that big of a deal to fall in love with someone?
Is true love something you can brag about?
Unforgettable Love Scene
What does it mean "to love", anyway?
That idiot!
Onii-chan?
Sorry!
Good morning.
I'm sorry about last night,
for suddenly barging in on you.
I'll be careful next time.
The movie—
let's go see another one.
But you have to go home with me this time.
What?
Nothing.
A gentle dream
yasashii yume ga
やさしい夢が
calls the spring in my heart
sotto mune no haru wo yobi
そっと胸の春を呼び
and becomes a gentle breeze
yasashii kaze ni nari
やさしい風になり
that touches you, then leaves.
kimi ni furete satteyuku
君に触れて去ってゆく
In the small pot
chiisana potto ni wa
小さなポットには
are feelings of love
daisukina kimochi
大好きな気持ち
swaying softly.
yurayura to
ゆらゆらと
They carry a sweet scent,
ii kaori nosete
いい香りのせて
always waiting,
itsumo matteita
いつも待っていた
warming up this moment.
kono toki wo atatamete
この時をあたためて
We understand each other
futari dakara wakaru koto
ふたりだからわかる
without words.
kotoba janakute
言葉じゃなくて
We just smile and hope
hohoemu dake negaudake
ほほえむだけ　願うだけ
to the peaceful sky.
shizukana sora e
しずかな空へ
Hope that we’ll see each other again tomorrow
ashita mo mata aeru yo ne
あしたもまた会えるよね
to the peaceful sky.
shizukana sora de
しずかな空で